https://1stcom.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - 1stcom Web Hosting - F5 / MVH Internet Services
Home // Privacy Policy - 1stcom Web Hosting - F5 / MVH Internet Services
F5 / MVH Internet Services PRIVACY POLICY
F5/MVH is firmly committed to the privacy of our clients. We have developed the following policy to disclose the information gathering and dissemination practices for this site.
We collect certain information from clients for billing and administrative functions. None of the information collected for these functions is provided to any outside party for any reason. From time to time we receive inquiries for examples of sites hosted by our service. If you would like to have your site available for such use, please contact
support@f5hosting.com. No information other than your sitename will be provided to the individual making the inquiry.
Personal information that may be displayed on the client site is the responsibility of the client. Security measures are in place to protect against loss, alteration, or misuse of data collected. Clients are responsible for ensuring that only they or their authorized designees utilize their accounts. Suspected incidents of unauthorized use of a client account should be reported immediately to our Abuse Investigations department at
abuse@f5hosting.com for attention.
This site contains links to resources outside the F5hosting.com web site. F5hosting.com is not responsible for the content of those sites.
Questions regarding the policy outlined in this document should be addressed to
support@f5hosting.com.
We will, from time to time, log in to certain Cpanels to check on things to ensure everything is running correctly. No information is compromised nor do we “check up” on clients. These are strictly cases of server maintenance.
Acceptable Use Policy
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
Copyright © 2020 1stcom Web Hosting – F5 / MVH Internet Services
